heinnie.com 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy | Heinnie Haynes

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we've provided this document explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this policy easy to find, we've made it available from the main navigation menu on our website.

### Collection of Personal Information

When visiting Heinnie Haynes, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small file which can be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once the file is added the cookie helps us analyse web traffic and additionally helps us provide you with a more customised experience. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

As one of our marketing methods, we use Google Adwords to drive traffic to the Heinnie Haynes web site. In order to measure the effectiveness of any campaigns we run under the Google Adwords program we use cookies to help us determine which ads are successfully leading to sales. The Adwords tracking cookies do not supply us with any personally identifiable information.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website experience by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website.

### Links to third party websites

If we have included links on this site to any other sites it is for your personal use and reference only. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

The Heinnie Haynes web site Privacy Policy is a live document and will evolve and change to meet changes in technology and new business practices and as such Heinnie Haynes reserves the right to make changes, amendments and updates at any time.

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy of Heinnie Haynes or any information that Heinnie Haynes holds on you then you may contact us at:

**Address: Heinnie Haynes**  
 **Unit C Atlantic Gate,**  
 **Atlantic Trading Estate**  
 **BARRY**  
 **CF63 3RF**  
 **United Kingdom**

**Phone: 033 0300 0400**  
 **International: +44 1446 722500**  
 **Fax: 033 0300 0401**

### What is this?

*Please note this service is in the Beta stage so you may receive messages that are unrelated to your chosen categories.

Get the latest news and products updates with Heinnie’s Push Notification service!

This service is a handy tool that keeps you up-to-date with all the latest news and offers that Heinnie has to offer! You’ll receive instant notifications about Heinnie news, such as:

Brand new items to Heinnie Haynes  
Item re-stock  
Special offers   
Clearance  
And more!

Once subscribed, you can pick and choose what categories you receive notifications for, making it personal to you. You can even turn the notifications on and off, at the flick of a switch.
